# MARK J. LINDSKOG

LinkedIn • Github • Portfolio • lindskogmarki@gmail.com • (567) 203-9473 • Columbus, OH 43204

# SUMMARY -----

Software Quality Assurance manual tester with coding experience, having previously completed a 6-month Full Stack Web Development Bootcamp through Ohio State University. I want to continue to learn and grow my skill set, as well as use my professional communication abilities to make an impact on teams.

# TECHNICAL SKILLS ———

Languages: Javascript ES6+, CSS3, HTML5, SQL, NoSQL

Applications: GitHub, MongoDB, MySQL, Heroku, TestRail, Jira, Insomnia, Postman

Tools: Express, Node, Query, Handlebars, React, Bootstrap, Foundation, MUI, Charles Proxy

# PROJECTS ———

Scriber | https://github.com/mjlindskog/scriber | https://powerful-shore-38656.herokuapp.com/

Summary: App for writers and note takers with text to speech functionality

Role: Front end author, text-to-speech implementer

Tools: Express, Node, JavaScript, MUI, React, Apollo GraphQL

### **EXPERIENCE -**

# **MoneyPigeon, Columbus, OH** | February 2022 - Present

#### Software QA Engineer

- Reviewing user interfaces for conformity and functionality by applying QA tools and methodologies
- Designing test cases in TestRail and providing test execution based on analysis of business requirements and specifications
- Configuring virtual devices applying BrowserStack, Android Studio and Xcode
- Identifying and reporting issues in Jira and monitoring defect status
- Designing data validation through a database with SQL-queries
- Performing API testing, creating collections and running different calls using Postman
- Collaborating with product manager and developers to meet the requirement and ensure a quality product

# **NuGrowth Solutions, Columbus, OH** | February 2020 - May 2021

## **Dedicated Tactic Group Campaign Representative**

- Representative for multiple accounts in the market daily, tripling number of impressions in the market
- ► Create interest and generate pipeline development within a 90-day client cycle for each account

#### **Inside Sales Representative**

- Contact to closure representative for UCaaS/Webinar platform provider (Onstream Media)
- Create over 250 impressions into the market each week through phone and email
- Product expert responsible for qualifying prospects and running through demonstrations

## **EDUCATION & CERTIFICATIONS –**

Project Management Institute | Disciplined Agile and Scrum Master | 2022

**Ohio State University** | Coding Web Development Certificate | 2021

Ohio University - Athens, OH | Bachelor of Arts - History | 2015 - 2019